{
    "subject": "resource/The_Remains_of_the_Day_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/James_Ivory_(director)",
    "human_readable": "The film 'The Remains of the Day' was directed by James Ivory.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9196189045906067,
            "question": "Name a film directed by James Ivory."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9090624451637268,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'The Remains of the Day'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9060890674591064,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by James Ivory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8818551301956177,
            "question": "Is James Ivory known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7681834101676941,
            "question": "What other films has James Ivory directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4953370988368988,
            "question": "What is the story about in 'The Remains of the Day'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48045313358306885,
            "question": "Who were the actors in 'The Remains of the Day'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45588892698287964,
            "question": "When was 'The Remains of the Day' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27292272448539734,
            "question": "What genre is 'The Remains of the Day' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18047168850898743,
            "question": "What awards has James Ivory won for his work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film 'The Remains of the Day' was directed by James Ivory.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5022_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is 'The Remains of the Day' likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5022_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'The Remains of the Day' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5022_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were the actors in 'The Remains of the Day'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5022_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5022_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5022_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5022_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5022_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5022_153.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5022_154.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5022_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5022_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5022_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5022_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the context information provided, which explicitly states \"Directed by James Ivory\" in multiple documents related to the film \"The Remains of the Day.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}